flags.net 2003-12-05

# World Flag Database: Contact Us

Contact Us   

**COPYRIGHT NOTICE**

  Please note that all the images used on this website are protected by copyright. All rights are reserved. You may use the images for non-commercial research use and you may use up to four of the images in your own web site. If you wish to use more of the images please contact the [World Flag Database](mailto:graham@flags.net) at the above address. You can purchase the original EPS files from which these images were generated from Flag Institute Enterprises Ltd.. FIE also sells Flag Specification Sheets that give precise details on colour and design for flag manufacturers.

**DISCLAIMER**

  Whilst every effort has been made to ensure that the information on this website is accurate, no responsiblity can be accepted for any loss or damage, howsoever caused, resulting from the use of the information provided.

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

  It is World Flag Database policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and email address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request).

**No Release of Information to Third Parties**  
Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as forwarding your query to an appropriate expert or to a supplier able to meet your requirements, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.

**No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**  
Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not email addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our site. This information is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff.

In addition, our website tracks information about the visits to it. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our site, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our website, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

Please note that the Flag Shop uses cookies to keep track of your shopping basket.
